Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nguyennlt (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Human Resources
Management
Recruiting

Languages

English

Certifications

Critical Thinking and Problem Solving

How to Support Your Employees' Well-Being

Establishing a Well-Being Program in Your Organization

Thy Nguyên Nại Lê

HR Operations Manager

Vietnam

Summary

Experienced Human Resources Team Lead with a demonstrated history of working in the banking industry. Skilled in Human Resources, Management, Customer Service, Banking, and Teamwork. Strong human resources professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Business Administration and Management, General from Huflit University.

Experience

HSBC

HR Operations Manager November 2022 - Present (2 years 5 months) Vietnam

s6k Labs HR Manager January 2022 - November 2022 (11 months) Vietnam

Prudential Vietnam Assurance Private Ltd. HR Governance & Vendor Management March 2020 - January 2022 (1 year 11 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Vietnam Prosperity Bank - VPBank 6 years 9 months HR Team Lead August 2017 - March 2020 (2 years 8 months)

Senior Executive HR March 2016 - September 2017 (1 year 7 months)

Executive HR July 2013 - March 2016 (2 years 9 months)

Education

Huflit University

Bachelor's degree, Business Administration and Management, General \cdot (2009 - 2013)